Marc Brown Papers MS148
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Arthur print material, 1994 -- 2007; 1994 -- 2000; MS148.001; 49 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s) Disk image available for reading room access.
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, script, second draft, 2000; MS148.001.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, script, third draft, 2000; MS148.001.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, script, outline, 2000; MS148.001.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1999; MS148.001.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, incidental character model package, clean, 1999; MS148.001.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, location designs/backgrounds, clean, 1999; MS148.001.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, oversized location designs/backgrounds, clean, 1999; MS148.001.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, incidental character model package with color models and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, backgrounds, color and background log, 1999; MS148.001.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, incidental character model package, rough, 1999; MS148.001.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, incidental character model package, rough, 1999; MS148.001.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - 85B: Arthur's family feud, storyboard, dyaxis, 2000; MS148.001.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - 86A: D.W.'s backpack mishap, incidental character/props model package, rough, 2000; MS148.001.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - 86A: D.W.'s backpack mishap, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - 86A: D.W.'s backpack mishap, storyboard, rough, 2000; MS148.001.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - 86A: D.W.'s backpack mishap, oversized location designs/backgrounds, rough, 2000; MS148.001.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - 86A: D.W.'s backpack mishap, script, outline, 2000; MS148.001.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - 86A: D.W.'s backpack mishap; 86B: Sue Ellen gets her goose cooked, notes on sound, music, and animation, 2001; MS148.001.018.00037 (Box 18)
  - 86B: Sue Ellen gets her goose cooked, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.018.00038 (Box 18)
  - 86B: Sue Ellen gets her goose cooked, incidental character/props model package, rough, 2000; MS148.001.018.00039 (Box 18)
  - 86B: Sue Ellen gets her goose cooked, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.018.00040 (Box 18)
  - 86B: Sue Ellen gets her goose cooked, oversized location designs/backgrounds, rough, 2000; MS148.001.018.00042 (Box 18)
  - 87A: Best of the nest, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.018.00043 (Box 18)
    Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-548#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-410#00002 and MS148/002-411#00002.
  - 87A: Best of the nest, incidental character/props model package, rough and props/characters design log, 2000; MS148.001.018.00044 (Box 18)
  - 87A: Best of the nest, storyboard, rough, 2000; MS148.001.018.00045 (Box 18)
  - 87A: Best of the nest, oversized location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.018.00047 (Box 18)
  - 87B: The secret life of dogs and babies, incidental/main character model package and props/characters design log, 2000; MS148.001.018.00048 (Box 18)
    Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-548#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-414#00002, MS148/002-415#00002, and MS148/002-416#00002.
  - 87B: The secret life of dogs and babies, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.018.00049 (Box 18)
  - 87B: The secret life of dogs and babies, storyboard, rough, 2000; MS148.001.018.00050 (Box 18)
  - 87B: The secret life of dogs and babies, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.018.00052 (Box 18)
  - 87B: The secret life of dogs and babies, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.018.00053 (Box 18)
  - 88A: Arthur plays the blues, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.018.00054 (Box 18)
    Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-549#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-412#00001 and MS148/002-413#00001.
  - 88A: Arthur plays the blues, notes on color models, 2000; MS148.001.018.00055 (Box 18)
  - 88A: Arthur plays the blues, main character/props model package, rough and props/characters design log, 2000; MS148.001.018.00056 (Box 18)
  - 88A: Arthur plays the blues, incidental character/props model package and reused characters log, 2000; MS148.001.018.00057 (Box 18)
  - 88A: Arthur plays the blues, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.018.00058 (Box 18)
  - 88B: Buster's sweet success, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.018.00059 (Box 18)
    Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-549#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-412#00002 and MS148/002-413#00002.
  - 88B: Buster's sweet success, main character color lineup and Prunella model rotation, 2000; MS148.001.018.00060 (Box 18)
  - 88B: Buster's sweet success, main character/props model package, rough and props/characters design log, 2000; MS148.001.018.00061 (Box 18)
  - 88B: Buster's sweet success, color models, 2001; MS148.001.018.00062 (Box 18)
  - 88B: Buster's sweet success, props model package and reused characters log, 2000; MS148.001.018.00063 (Box 18)
  - 88B: Buster's sweet success, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.018.00064 (Box 18)
  - 88B: Buster's sweet success, storyboard, sheet direction, 2000; MS148.001.018.00065 (Box 18)
  - Individual and group commercial bumpers, 1999; MS148.001.018.00066 (Box 18)
  - Arthur story themes and values, 2001; MS148.001.018.00067 (Box 18)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, cover poster, 2000; MS148.001.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, backgrounds, color and Baxter day song location design log, 2000; MS148.001.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, notes on music, sound, and animation, part I, 2000; MS148.001.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, notes on music, sound, and animation, part II, 2000; MS148.001.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, incidental/main character model package with color models, part I of II, 1999; MS148.001.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, incidental/main character model package with color models, part II of II, 1999; MS148.001.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, incidental/main character model package with color models, additional props and characters, 1999; MS148.001.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, ink sketch of Uncle Fred in Hawaiian shirt, 1999; MS148.001.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, incidental/main character model package, clean, part I of II, 1999; MS148.001.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, incidental/main character model package, clean, part II of II, 1999; MS148.001.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, location designs/backgrounds, clean, 1999; MS148.001.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, props/main character model package, rough, 1999; MS148.001.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, notes on music and sound, 2000; MS148.001.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, Baxter daysong, props/incidental character model package, clean, 1999; MS148.001.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, location designs/backgrounds, rough and notes on location designs, 1999; MS148.001.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, location designs/backgrounds, clean, pages I-10 and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part I, props/incidental character model package with color models, comments for color models, 1999; MS148.001.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, backgrounds, color, 1999; MS148.001.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, main/incidental character model package with color models, pages 218-345, 1999; MS148.001.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, Read family gift exchange, incidental/main character model package, clean and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, Francine's family, main/incidental character model package, clean and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, dog fight over present sequence, props/main character model package, clean and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, Santa Claus, incidental/main character model package, clean and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, Buster-Christmas morning (cyber trout), main character model package, clean and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, Muffy's song, main character model package, clean and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, Buster brunch I, props/incidental character model package, clean and props characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, resolution, incidental/main character model package, clean and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, Buster brunch 2, main character model package, clean and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, Muffy and Brain, main characater model package, clean and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, parade and broken bird, main characater model package, clean and props/characters design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00030 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 2000; MS148.001.019.00031 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, props/incidental character model package, rough, 1999; MS148.001.019.00032 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, ink sketch of revised Uncle Fred, 1999; MS148.001.019.00033 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, rough ink sketch of Arthur characters and comments about production schedule, 2000; MS148.001.019.00034 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, part II, location designs/backgrounds, clean and location design log, 1999; MS148.001.019.00035 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, comments on Arthur's voice, 2000; MS148.001.019.00036 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, all sections, storyboard, rough, pages 1-104, 1999; MS148.001.019.00037 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, all sections, storyboard, cleaned-up, pages 1-84, 1999; MS148.001.019.00038 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, all sections, storyboard, cleaned-up, pages 85-185, 1999; MS148.001.019.00039 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, all sections, storyboard, cleaned-up, pages 185-263/Buster's song, 1999; MS148.001.019.00040 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, all sections, storyboard, cleaned-up, pages 294-360, 1999; MS148.001.019.00041 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, all sections, storyboard, cleaned-up, pages 361-480, 1999; MS148.001.019.00042 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, all sections, storyboard, cleaned-up/dyaxis, pages 481-589, 1999; MS148.001.019.00043 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section B, storyboard, cleaned-up/dyaxis, pages 264-293, 1999; MS148.001.019.00044 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section B, storyboard, faxed copy, cleaned-up/dyaxis, pages 264-293, 2000; MS148.001.019.00045 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section G, storyboard, rough, pages 1-123, 1999; MS148.001.019.00046 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section K, storyboard, rough, pages 1-88, 1999; MS148.001.019.00047 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section BS, storyboard, rough, pages 269-286, 1999; MS148.001.019.00048 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section J, storyboard, rough, pages 1-37, 1999; MS148.001.019.00049 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, all sections, storyboard with corrections, faxed copy, 2000; MS148.001.019.00050 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section L, storyboard, rough, pages 1-9, 1999; MS148.001.019.00051 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section M, storyboard, rough, pages 1-32, 1999; MS148.001.019.00052 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section N, storyboard, rough, pages 1-33, 1999; MS148.001.019.00053 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section O, storyboard, rough, pages 1-18., 1999; MS148.001.019.00054 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section O, storyboard, rough, pages 1-10., 1999; MS148.001.019.00055 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section P, R, Q and S, comments and corrections for rough storyboards, 2000; MS148.001.019.00056 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, comments on color choices for PTI storyboard, 2000; MS148.001.019.00057 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section P, storyboard, rough, pages 1-16, 1999; MS148.001.019.00058 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section Q, storyboard, rough, pages 1-5, 2000; MS148.001.019.00059 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section R, storyboard, rough, pages 1-42, 1999; MS148.001.019.00060 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section S, storyboard, rough, pages 1-26, 2000; MS148.001.019.00061 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section U, storyboard, rough, pages 1-16, 1999; MS148.001.019.00062 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section V, storyboard, rough, pages 1-9, 1999; MS148.001.019.00063 (Box 19)
  - Arthur's perfect Christmas, section W, storyboard, rough, pages 1-9, 1999; MS148.001.019.00064 (Box 19)
  - 89A: Muffy's soccer shocker, storyboard, rough, 2000; MS148.001.020.00001 (Box 20)
    Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-552#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-176#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-417#00001, MS148/002-418#00001, and MS148/002-419#00001.
  - 89A: Muffy's soccer shocker, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - 89A: Muffy's soccer shocker, incidental character model package, rough and props/characters design log, 2000; MS148.001.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - 89A: Muffy's soccer shocker, storyboard, dyaxis, 2001; MS148.001.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - 89B: The boy who cried comet, incidental character/props model package, rough and props/characters design log, 2001; MS148.001.020.00005 (Box 20)
    Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-552#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-176#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-420#00001 and MS148/002-421#00001.
  - 89B: The boy who cried comet, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - 89B: The boy who cried comet, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2001; MS148.001.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - 89B: The boy who cried comet, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - Kideo Video: Arthur's new friend, storyboard, 2000; MS148.001.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - Kideo Video: Arthur's new friend, main character model package with color models and props/characters design log, 2000; MS148.001.020.00010 (Box 20)
  - Kideo Video: Arthur's new friend, storyboard, dyaxis, 2000; MS148.001.020.00011 (Box 20)
  - Kideo Video: Arthur's new friend, backgrounds, color, 2000; MS148.001.020.00012 (Box 20)
  - Kideo Video: Arthur's new friend, script, third draft (design), 2000; MS148.001.020.00013 (Box 20)
  - Kideo Video: Arthur's new friend, script, first draft, 2000; MS148.001.020.00014 (Box 20)
  - Kideo Video: Arthur's new friend, location designs/backgrounds, clean and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.020.00015 (Box 20)
  - Kideo Video: Arthur's new friend, main character model package, clean, 2000; MS148.001.020.00016 (Box 20)
  - Kideo Video: Arthur's new friend, notes on animation, 2000; MS148.001.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - 90A: Brother, can you spare a clarinet?, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.020.00018 (Box 20)
    Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-553#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-177#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-417#00002, MS148/002-418#00002, and MS148/002-419#00002.
  - 90A: Brother, can you spare a clarinet?, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.020.00019 (Box 20)
  - 90A: Brother, can you spare a clarinet?, incidental character model package, rough, 2001; MS148.001.020.00020 (Box 20)
  - 90A: Brother, can you spare a clarinet?, location designs/backgrounds, clean, 2001; MS148.001.020.00021 (Box 20)
  - 90A: Brother, can you spare a clarinet?, incidental character/props model package, clean and props/characters design log, 2001; MS148.001.020.00022 (Box 20)
  - 90B: Prunella's special edition, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.020.00023 (Box 20)
    Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-553#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-177#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-414#00001, MS148/002-415#00001, and MS148/002-416#00001.
  - 90B: Prunella's special edition, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2001; MS148.001.020.00024 (Box 20)
  - 90B: Prunella's special edition, ink sketch of Henry, 2001; MS148.001.020.00025 (Box 20)
  - 90B: Prunella's special edition, incidental character/props model package, rough, 2001; MS148.001.020.00026 (Box 20)
  - 90B: Prunella's special edition, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.020.00027 (Box 20)
  - 91A: For whom the bell tolls, script, first draft, 2000; MS148.001.020.00028 (Box 20)
  - 91A: For whom the bell tolls, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.020.00029 (Box 20)
  - 91A: For whom the bell tolls, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.020.00030 (Box 20)
  - 91A: For whom the bell tolls, main character/props model package, rough and props/characters design log, 2000; MS148.001.020.00031 (Box 20)
  - 91A: For whom the bell tolls, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.020.00032 (Box 20)
  - 91B: Arthur and los vecinos, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 2001; MS148.001.020.00033 (Box 20)
  - 91B: Arthur and los vecinos, main character/props model package, rough and props/characters design log, 2001; MS148.001.020.00034 (Box 20)
  - 91B: Arthur and los vecinos, notes on episode content, 2001; MS148.001.020.00035 (Box 20)
  - 91B: Arthur and los vecinos, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.020.00036 (Box 20)
  - 91B: Arthur and los vecinos, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.020.00037 (Box 20)
  - 91B: Arthur and los vecinos, notes on props/location designs, 2000; MS148.001.020.00038 (Box 20)
  - 92A: The boy with his head in the clouds, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.020.00039 (Box 20)
    Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-021#00001-00004 and MS148/001-021#00010-00011. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-554#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-179#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-425#00001, MS148/002-426#00001, and MS148/002-427#00001.
  - 92A: The boy with his head in the clouds, script, first draft, 2001; MS148.001.020.00040 (Box 20)
  - 92A: The boy with his head in the clouds, script, second draft, 2001; MS148.001.021.00001 (Box 21)
    Associated production files can be found at MS148/001-020#00039-00040 and MS148/001-021#00010-00011. Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-554#00001. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-179#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-425#00001, MS148/002-426#00001, and MS148/002-427#00001.
  - 92A: The boy with his head in the clouds, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.021.00002 (Box 21)
  - 92A: The boy with his head in the clouds, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.021.00003 (Box 21)
  - 92A: The boy with his head in the clouds, incidental character/props model package, rough and props/characters design log, 2000; MS148.001.021.00004 (Box 21)
  - 92B: Citizen Frensky, script, outline, 2001; MS148.001.021.00005 (Box 21)
    Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-554#00002. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-179#00002. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/002-422#00001, MS148/002-423#00001, and MS148/002-424#00001.
  - 92B: Citizen Frensky, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.021.00006 (Box 21)
  - 92B: Citizen Frensky, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.021.00007 (Box 21)
  - 92B: Citizen Frensky, main/incidental character model package, clean with props/characters design log, 2000; MS148.001.021.00008 (Box 21)
  - 92B: Citizen Frensky, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.021.00009 (Box 21)
  - 92A: The boy with his head in the clouds; 92B: Citizen Frensky; 93B: More!, notes on color, 2001; MS148.001.021.00010 (Box 21)
    Associated first cut can be found at MS148/002-554. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/002-179. Associated production files for The boy with his head in the clouds can be found at MS148/001-020#00039-00040 and MS148/001-021#00001-00004. Associated first cut for The boy with his head in the clouds can be found at MS148/002-554#00001. Associated mix for approval for The boy with his head in the clouds can be found at MS148/002-179#00001. Associated tapes for The boy with his head in the clouds can be found at MS148/002-425#00001, MS148/002-426#00001, and MS148/002-427#00001. Associated first cut for Citizen Frensky can be found at MS148/002-554#00002. Associated mix for approval for Citizen Frensky can be found at MS148/002-179#00002. Associated tapes for Citizen Frensky can be found at MS148/002-422#00001, MS148/002-423#00001, and MS148/002-424#00001.
  - 92A: The boy with his head in the clouds; 92B: Citizen Frensky; 94A: Rhyme for your life; 94B: A good sport, notes on color models, background keys, and final storyboards, 2001; MS148.001.021.00011 (Box 21)
  - 93A: Friday the 13th, script, second draft, 2001; MS148.001.021.00012 (Box 21)
  - 93A: Friday the 13th, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.021.00013 (Box 21)
  - 93A: Friday the 13th, main character/props model package, clean and props/characters design log, 2001; MS148.001.021.00014 (Box 21)
  - 93A: Friday the 13th, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.021.00015 (Box 21)
  - 93A: Friday the 13th, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.021.00016 (Box 21)
  - 93A: Friday the 13th; 93B: More!, notes on character/props color models and background keys, 2001; MS148.001.021.00017 (Box 21)
  - 93B: More!, main character/props model package, rough and props/characters design log, 2000; MS148.001.021.00018 (Box 21)
  - 93B: More!, location designs/ backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.021.00019 (Box 21)
  - 93B: More!, script, third draft, 2001; MS148.001.021.00020 (Box 21)
  - 93B: More!, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.021.00021 (Box 21)
  - 94A: Rhyme for your life, storyboard, sheet direction, 2001; MS148.001.021.00022 (Box 21)
  - 94A: Rhyme for your life, storyboard, rough, 2001; MS148.001.021.00023 (Box 21)
  - 94A: Rhyme for your life, main character/props model package, rough, 2000; MS148.001.021.00024 (Box 21)
  - 94A: Rhyme for your life, script, outline, 2001; MS148.001.021.00025 (Box 21)
  - 94A: Rhyme for your life, location designs/backgrounds, rough and location design log, 2000; MS148.001.021.00026 (Box 21)